LUU VAN HUY

Fullstack developer



I am a Fullstack java developer and have more than 5 years of experience working in software development. In addition to the field of programming, I have more than 2 years working as a team leader position. I have over 2 years working with major cloud providers like GCP, AWS and DO. I often work in systems that require a large number of cocurrent users and have experience in both programming and server management, so analyzing, designing and implementing performance optimization systems is my strong point.

Work experience

SEN

4/2021 - now

TEAN LEADER

Main responsibilities:

- · Set up and manage company production servers
- · Project management, division of work
- · Analysis and design of new features
- · Learn to develop application technology to the system
- · Environment setting and build process design
- · Participate in designing and setting up infrastructure for new projects
- · Design and integration with 3rd systems

Main projects:

- Learning management system
- · Meeting management system
- · Online conference tool system
- · Interactive Content Management System

Technology used:

- · Java (spring boot, spring mvc, spring security,...), Nodejs
- Reactjs
- Meteoris
- · postgresql, mongodb, redis

SEN

9/2020 - 4/2021

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Main responsibilities:

- · Participate in feature development and system bug fixes
- · Design and integration with 3rd systems

Main projects:

· Learning management system

Technology used:

- Java (spring boot, spring mvc, spring security,...), Nodejs
- Reactjs

AureoleInformationTechnology

Inc

2018 - 2020

SOFTWARE ENGINER

Main responsibilities:

- Develop business management software based on web interface using J2EE, J2EE and Web font end technology like JSF, javascript.
- Develop a vehicle resercation system based on microservice architecture using java spring boot framework.

- Develop hybrid app using Ionic (Angular and cordova).
- System development on open faas platform (python)

Technology used:

- · Java (spring boot), J2EE, FSF, python
- Angular

Education

2014 - 2018

MAJOR: SOFTWARE ENGINEER

TON DUC THANG UNIVERSITY

Skills

Back-End

- · Java (Spring boot, Spring mvc, J2EE,...)
- · Node JS

Font-End

- · Html, css, js,...
- · Angular/ react

DATABASE

- PostgresSql
- Oracle
- · MongoDB
- Redis

Cloud Server

- Have more 2 years working with Google, Digital Ocean, AWS.
- Have experience set up production mode in Ubuntu/CentOS
 - + Tomcat/ Wildfly Jboss
 - + Postgres db, mongo db
 - + Node Js/ react, angular application
- Have experience in set up load balancer, cloudfront, cdn, google storage, S3, firebase,...

Other

- Redis, MQTT, elastic search, firebase,...